h1. Kobayashi Maru Commander 小林丸指揮官 v1.0 開發者的話

[[開發日誌]]

h1. Kobayashi Maru Commander 小林丸指揮官 v1.0 開發者的話

# 本專案已經是最後一次重大發布。目前著手開放原始碼的計畫。感謝各位的支持。
# 有別於故事關卡，本版本新增了沒有勝利條件可以不斷遊玩的生存關卡，以及配合挑戰關卡的主角船選擇模式。
# 本版本將多國語言特色正式實裝，將之前的雙語並列的圖片文字整個移除。全部改採Unity的文字系統。
# 給各位參考，本專案開發自20120914至20130215共歷時五個月計工時604小時（折合75.5工作天）。

h1. Kobayashi Maru Commander 小林丸指揮官 v1.0 from/for Developers

# This release is final of this project, and I am processing the open source issue. Thanks for all players with me.
# Better than the story mode, this version add a challenge mode of survival, and main character ship selection.
# The feature of multi-language has been implemented, all pictures for texts with both language are removed.
# The total working hours of this project is 604 hours from 20120914 to 20130215.